If you want to edit one of your projects in general,
you must first select the package you want to modify.
The selected package becomes highlighted
and its contents are displayed on the right side.
Use the "Edit project" button located on the right to start your editing process.
If you want to upload your data to a specific folder,
you must first select that folder.
You can add your data in two ways, using either "File Upload" or "Import".
With "Import" you can add data from external data sources,
such as databases or repositories.
In order to log in, you have to select the corresponding entry,
here the database "EasyDB".
To access your data, enter your external source username and password.
After the login, all your files in the external source will be displayed on the right.
Here you can see two folders on the database system containing the data.
To upload your files first select the appropriate folder.
There are two different ways to import your files into the FDOrganizer:
either "Import selected" or "Import all".
To upload only individual selected files at first select the relevant file
by clicking on it.
Then use the Button "Import selected".
As soon as the import is complete, the files are displayed on the left.
In addition to the file name, you can also see the size of each file.
If you want to import all your files in your external source at once,
use the "Import all" button.
If necessary, you can also delete your files after they have been uploaded.
Just use the recycle bin symbol.
When you click on the symbol, a dialogue box will offer you two options.
You can either keep your file by selecting "Do not delete"
or delete it by selecting "Delete file".
In this case, your data will only be deleted from the FDOrganizer.
It will not be deleted in your external source,
so if you want to restore the file, you can import it again.